<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Patient Portal</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dash">DashActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="rupee">\u20B9</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="our_mission">- We conduct spot admission on behalf of the institutes at our offices.\n- A Complete marketing support to the University/Board/Institutions for conducting admissions.\n-Providing required information to the aspirants about course/college/university/country/place etc.\n- Identifying appropriate course/institute which meet student needs.\n- Facilitating determination of eligibility of students.\n- Arranging provisional admission offers from institutions.\n- Facilitating departure formalities.</string>
    <string name="about_us">Dentomax International Academy Subcenter of Delhi Institute of Healthcare and Research is one of the pioneer institutes serving the educational cause and the unique needs of working professionals. It was given accreditation status shortly after its foundation. We are offereing Admission Career Counseling Guidance in all sectors of education. We provide all career counseling and admission guidance to aspirants regarding Teaching, Engineering, Medical, Management, Para-medical and other non-traditional fields in India.
We are the authorised admission and couseling centers for several Universities recognized by UGC, HRD, AIU, DEC, AICTC and Government of India. We also offer Masters, Associate and Doctorate Degree programs, each with a wide range of majors. Our curriculum is kept fully adreast of all the latest technology advances, allowing working adults to realize their career aspirations and self-enhancement goals. We are operational since 2008 with cooperate office located at New Delhi.</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>